nonvegjokes.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Downtown Host

We at Downtown Host Inc. (“Downtown Host”, and sometimes also referred to in this policy as “we”, “us”, or “our”) are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of the Personal Information of all our employees, customers as well as visitors to our website - www.downtownhost.com or our client or support portals at my.downtownhost.com and support.downtownhost.com (collectively, the “Sites”). As a part of that commitment, Downtown Host has implemented this Privacy Policy to apply to the Sites so that you know what information about you we collect, why we collect it, how we use that information, and the choices we offer, including how to access and update information. Your privacy matters to us, so please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions, our contact email addresses are provided at the end of this document. 

## How We Collect Your Personal Information

When you visit our Sites and submit a request to receive information concerning our services you will be asked to provide personal information (such as name, email address, telephone number and mailing address) for the purpose of administering your request and contacting you.

In addition, all customers or visitors to our Sites have the option to register for our newsletter and special offers subscription (referred to in this paragraph as our “Newsletter”) by entering their e-mail address along with their first and last name. Upon completing your Newsletter subscription, You consent to our occasionally informing you about our special hosting offers and company news by way of e-mail to your subscribed email address. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters or special offers e-mails, you can unsubscribe at any time by using the link ‘unsubscribe’ on the newsletter or special offer e-mail. After receiving the unsubscribe request, we will delete your email address from the distribution list, thus preventing you from receiving any further newsletters or special offer e-mails from us. We use a 3rd party provider called “MailChimp” to store your subscribed email addresses along with your first and last name (if you chose to provide that information during the sign-up). Therefore, by providing your email address and name to us for the purpose of receiving our Newsletter, you automatically agree to all of MailChimp’s legal policies located at https://mailchimp.com/legal/

We request information from you on our order form. To order a service from us, you must provide certain contact (ex. your name and address) and financial (ex. credit card number) information.

Finally, we may collect information voluntarily provided by you, via the Sites or otherwise, for the purposes of customer support and feedback.

## When We Disclose Your Personal Information

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, Downtown Host does not disclose, give, rent or sell your personal information collected through the Sites’ to any third party other than its paying agent and support agents. Access to your personal information is restricted to Downtown Host employees, representatives or agents. 

Agents appointed by Downtown Host to assist with or operate the Sites or administer the Sites’ support and marketing programs will have access to your personal information for these purposes. Such agents are required by Downtown Host to comply with the provisions of this Privacy Policy and are prohibited from disclosing personal information to third parties except as required by law. 

Downtown Host reserves the right to co-operate fully with local, provincial, state, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any personal information (including private electronic communications transmitted on the Sites) or any purported unlawful activities. 

Downtown Host reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual sale, merger or other transfer of the assets or shares of Downtown Host, an affiliate or division thereof, provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the principles expressed in this Privacy Policy and the personal information does not constitute all or substantially all of the assets being transferred.
